<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tech_App-Final</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">In Ear Monitor</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Keyboard</string>
    
    <string name="brand_iem">Knowledge Zenith</string>
    <string name="brand_iem1">Moondrop</string>
    <string name="brand_iem2">Tanchjim</string>
    <string name="brand_iem3">Tin Hi-Fi</string>
    <string name="brand_iem4">Sony Audio</string>
    <string name="brand_iem5">CCA</string>
    <string name="brand_iem6">TRN</string>
    <string name="brand_iem7">Final Audio</string>

    <string name="brand_ky">Fantech</string>
    <string name="brand_ky1">Rexus</string>
    <string name="brand_ky2">Keychron</string>
    <string name="brand_ky3">Logitech</string>
    <string name="brand_ky4">Asus ROG</string>
    <string name="brand_ky5">Razer</string>
    <string name="brand_ky6">Steelseries</string>

    <string name="comment_">Sound Quality - KZ AST. In my eyes, this is the best
        sounding earphone KZ has ever produced. Detail monster balanced armature sound but
        with surprisingly good quality and quantity bass. KZ got famous for their
        price to performance, and this earphone finally hits that spot that
        so many of its predecessors failed on.</string>

    <string name="comment_1">The content is rich and of high quality. 
        The Variations come with 3 pairs of foam tips and 3 pairs of silicone tips. 
        Additionally, there are replacement filters with adhesive, included in the package. 
        Moondrop also provides you with a plastic tool to help you precisely 
        place those filters on the nozzle.</string>
    
    <string name="comment_2">Just a whiff more elevated than sub-bass,
        so still modest in absolute quantity, Tanchjim Oxygen mid bass is fast,
        seriously punchy and detailed. Its just about perfect for acoustic genres,
        while will be felt as lacking for EDM, hard rock and such.
        Clean and natural especially on the central part.</string>

    <string name="comment_3">Comfort levels are good with the Tin HiFi T5 and they are not probably
        the heaviest of the line but are definitely the largest of their entire T line of IEMs.
        You do feel them on but they do not present any discomfort
        wearing them for long periods of time.</string>

    <string name="comment_4">With its thick and full sound, the $799 Sony IER-M7 offers
        a solid IEM for anyone in need of detail and accuracy.
        While the neutral, workaday sound may not be the stuff every audiophile dreams of,
        the M7 still offers inarguable value for folks who want to hear music in its purest,
        most unadulterated state.</string>

    <string name="comment_5">The CCA C16 for the money is an excellent-sounding balanced earphone
        that is capable of giving a very detailed and accurate representation of the source material.
        Unlike other modern ChiFi earphones which bump the bass a little and have a hint of warmth,
        these are much more neutral</string>

    <string name="comment_6">The TRN BA8’s PTSD inducing graph is admittedly scarier than it looks,
        but the tuning is still rather fatiguing and hot in 2 – 6 kHz regions, as per the graph.
        The tonality is also a bit off in the mids, with a very hollow lower mids.
        Having said that, the TRN BA8’s technicalities are very good.
        If technicalities are of more importance to you over tonality </string>

    <string name="username">Shrchse Lin</string>
    <string name="userEmail">2010817210028@mhs.ulm.ac.id</string>
    <string name="imagedesc">imageDesc</string>

</resources>